> > 布莱恩: 现在我们只做一个测试
&gt;&gt; Brian: So now we're gonna
do just a modicum of testing.
在测试开始之前我可能不是你想学的人
Before we get started in testing, I'm
probably not the person you wanna learn
因为我不喜欢测试我的代码
testing from because I don't really
like testing my code that much.
特别是，我不喜欢测试 UI 代码。
Specifically, I don't like
testing UI code a lot.
当我在 Netflix 工作的时候我在主页上工作
When I worked at Netflix,
I worked on the homepage, and there's so
在这个网页上每天不断变化的流通量
much flux in that homepage where it's
constantly changing day over day,
那个写测试是毫无意义的吧
that writing test for
it was pointless, right?
因为我们花了很多时间或更多的时间写测试
Because we'd spend as much time or
more time writing test and
那就在第二天我们又改头版的时候删了。
then just deleting them the next day
when we changed the front page again.
所以，这就是为什么我不写大量的测试来专门针对 React 代码，因为
So, that's why I don't write a lot of
tests for specifically React code, because
它改变了所有的时间，对我来说，没有太多的意义去做。
it changes all the time, and to me that
doesn't make a lot of sense to do that.
但我要说的是我们的 API 客户
But what I will say for
things like we have our API client,
我来测试下地狱吧
I'll test the hell out of that, right.
我将业务逻辑抽象为模块，并测试模块和
I'll abstract business logic into modules,
and I'll test the modules and
他们就不会测试 UI 代码了
then they won't test the UI code.
所以你还需要写前端测试，但是
So you still need to write
front end tests, but
对 UI 组件的要求不高。
just not as much for UI components.
说了，就像你有矛盾的问题，对吧 ?
That being said, like if you
have consistent problems, right?
例如， Facebook 不断地网站出现问题
So for example, Facebook constantly sites
have they have problems with showing
在错误的时间通知，对。
notifications at the wrong time, right.
所以他们做了很多测试
So they've wrote a lot of tests,
testing that specific things
例如确保它们在正确的时间显示通知。
like making sure that they show
notifications at the right time.
所以这也许是合适的。
So that might be appropriate.
我要教你怎么做
And I'm gonna show you how to do it and
那你就可以自己决定了
then you can make your
own decisions about it.
还有一个 kentc.cented on fronted masters ， is advanced React testing
Again there is a kentc.course on fronted
masters that is advanced React testing
在那里他深入研究了如何去做
where he goes into great
depth on how to do it.
我要用他的图书馆给你看一点点
And I'm actually gonna show you
a little bit using his library.
我觉得他是用 Jest 以外的东西我今天就用 Jest 了
I think he uses something other than Jest,
and I'm gonna use Jest today so
也许对你有用
that might be useful to you.
以前的这个课程我相信也用了莫查
Previous versions of this course
I believe used Mocha as well so
对你也很有意思
that's interesting to you as well.
我认为是使用莫查的 v3 或 v2 。
I think that's v3 or v2 that uses Mocha.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，我们要做的
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, so what we're gonna do
现在我们要说的是
right now is we're gonna say
npm install- 大写 D jest as as
npm install- capital D jest as
反应测试图书馆
well as react-test-library
>> Brian: 好，在您的源中
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, inside of your source
我们将创建名为 __tests__的新文件夹。
director we are going to create
a new folder called __tests__.
为什么双方都要双重下划线，要么是 duners?
Why double underscores on both sides,
or dunders?
我没说这就是他们叫的
I did not make that up,
that's what they're called.
这是一个 Python 的东西。
[LAUGH] It's a Python thing.
我认为它是从 Python 产生的，它可能是从 Python中存在的。
I think it arose from Python,
it might have been existing from Python.
这不是一个 JavaScript 的问题，它肯定是从 Python中得到的。
It's not a JavaScript thing,
it's definitely more from Python.
但这意味着魔法是吧
But it means magical, right?
所以如果你在两边都有下划线的话，基本就意味着什么东西
So if you have underscores on both sides,
it basically means something is looking
啊，这个这个要叫这个，对吧 ?
for this, so
it must be called this, right?
因此在此特定情况下， jest 将自动查找测试目录
So in this particular case, jest will
automatically find test directories
以这种方式命名并在它们内部运行测试，对吧 ?
named like this and
run tests inside of them, right?
所以如果我在这里创建一个新的文件
So if I create a new file here,
我仍然要叫我的 SearchParams >> Brian: .test.js，
I'm still gonna call mine SearchParams
&gt;&gt; Brian: .test.js,
但我可以叫它 SearchParameters.js
but I actually could just call
it SearchParameters.js, and
因为它在神奇的测试目录里是吧
it would still be found because it's
in the magical test directory, right?
>> Brian: 否则，它将查找名为 .test.js 或 .spec.js的文件。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Otherwise it will look for
files called .test.js, or .spec.js.
所以
So,